const quizData = [  {    question: "What is the national speed limit on single carriageway roads in the UK?",    answers: ["40 mph", "50 mph", "60 mph", "70 mph"],
    correctAnswer: "60 mph"
  },
  {
    question: "What does a triangular road sign with a red border indicate?",
    answers: ["Stop", "Yield", "Warning", "No entry"],
    correctAnswer: "Warning"
  },
  {
    question: "What does a blue circle road sign indicate?",
    answers: ["Speed limit", "Mandatory instructions", "Information", "Caution"],
    correctAnswer: "Mandatory instructions"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the UK legal limit for alcohol consumption while driving?",
    answers: ["50 milligrams of alcohol per 100 millilitres of blood", "60 milligrams of alcohol per 100 millilitres of blood", "70 milligrams of alcohol per 100 millilitres of blood", "80 milligrams of alcohol per 100 millilitres of blood"],
    correctAnswer: "80 milligrams of alcohol per 100 millilitres of blood (80mg/100ml)"
  },
  {
    question: "What do you need to display if you are driving a vehicle that is over three years old?",
    answers: ["A valid driving licence", "A valid insurance certificate", "A valid road tax disc", "A valid MOT certificate"],
    correctAnswer: "A valid MOT certificate"
  },
  {
    question: "What does a double yellow line on the side of the road indicate?",
    answers: ["No stopping or waiting", "No overtaking", "No entry", "No parking or waiting at any time"],
    correctAnswer: "No parking or waiting at any time"
  },
  {
    question: "What should you do if you see a pedestrian crossing the road ahead of you?",
    answers: ["Speed up and overtake", "Slow down and be prepared to stop", "Honk your horn", "Keep driving and ignore them"],
    correctAnswer: "Slow down and be prepared to stop"
  },
  {
    question: "What does a white diagonal stripe painted on the road indicate?",
    answers: ["A pedestrian crossing", "A roundabout", "A hazardous area or a slip road", "A parking zone"],
    correctAnswer: "A hazardous area or a slip road"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the penalty for using a mobile phone while driving in the UK?",
    answers: ["3 penalty points on your driving licence and a £100 fine", "6 penalty points on your driving licence and a £200 fine", "9 penalty points on your driving licence and a £300 fine", "12 penalty points on your driving licence and a driving ban"],
    correctAnswer: "6 penalty points on your driving licence and a £200 fine"
  },
  {
    question: "What should you do if you see an emergency vehicle with flashing lights and a siren approaching from behind?",
    answers: ["Ignore it and keep driving", "Speed up to get out of the way", "Pull over to the side of the road and let the vehicle pass", "Swerve around it"],
    correctAnswer: "Pull over to the side of the road and let the vehicle pass"
  }
];


export default quizData;
